[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "King Richard III killed his two nephews, which were later reported to have been seen as ghosts. What were their names?", "correct_answer": "Edward V of England and Richard of Shrewsbury", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael of Knottinghamm and Richard of Shrewsbury", "Edward the V of England and Michael of Knottinghamm", "Edward of Shrewsbury and Richard the V of England"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do you call a large group of islands?", "correct_answer": "Archipelago", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Islet", "Chanel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first facial hair appears in this area during puberty.", "correct_answer": "Corners of the upper lip", "incorrect_answers": ["Sides of the chin", "Lower jaw", "Under the lower lip"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous Hollywood actor portrayed drug lord Tony Montana in the 1983 crime drama movie Scarface?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Alec Baldwin", "Marlon Brando", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take Neptune to orbit the Sun once?", "correct_answer": "165 years", "incorrect_answers": ["211 years", "89 years", "128 years"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the two twin stars in the constellation Gemini?", "correct_answer": "Castor  Pollux", "incorrect_answers": ["Spica  Arcturus", "Voltron  Yularis", "Merak  Dubhe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements regarding the words imply and infer is correct?", "correct_answer": "The speaker implies, the listener infers", "incorrect_answers": ["All these statements are true", "Imply and infer mean exactly the same thing", "The speaker infers, the listener implies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this1990 film Lt. John J. Dunbar is accepted as an honorary member of the Sioux tribe and helps them locate a herd of buffalo.", "correct_answer": "Dances with Wolves", "incorrect_answers": ["At Play in the Fields of the Lord", "Grey Owl", "The Worlds Fastest Indian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country did the American Akita dog breed originate?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada", "China", "United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the size of Mars compared to the size of Earth.", "correct_answer": "Mars is smaller than Earth.", "incorrect_answers": ["The two planets can not be compared.", "They are the same size.", "Mars is bigger than Earth."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In December 2002, Calvin Klein sold his company to which fashion corporation?", "correct_answer": "Phillips Van Heusen Corp.", "incorrect_answers": ["Holding di Partecipazioni", "Abercrombie  Fitch", "Tommy Hilfiger Corp."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Snakes reproduce only by laying eggs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]